Drive off in your dream car.
My dream car,
Your eyes, nose lips.
Party time of flawless features,
Started stanning from one look.
The one who stole my heart,
Our little thunder tiger.
We adore you,
MONSTIEZ's superstar.
Hakuna Matata,
Today's host and final member.
The day I've been waiting for.
Welcome to Spotify,
The smartest Spotify record completed by BABYMONSTER.
Connecting right now.
Back with the 3rd Mini Album "CHOOM",
welcome BABYMONSTER!
[Faces of the next generation with limitless spectrum]
Everyone looks so pretty today.
[The host is looking gorgeous] You're beautiful too.
[Thanks]
I'll be your host today to lead a conversation
made for BABYMONSTER,
all about BABYMONSTER,
based on customized topics.
This will shake every detail out of BABYMONSTER.
[Shake] This will shake every detail out of BABYMONSTER.
[Ta-da]
[RORA's secret weapon]
With this, we'll create new stories together.
Why is this your secret weapon?
This shuffle table knows everything about us.
[Everything?]
For example, the member who ate jjimdak today.
[Oooh]
Or the member who went to an exhibition yesterday.
Who was it?
[They know this too?]
The member who went to watch a movie alone yesterday.
Who?
[The shuffle table knows all of this?]
It's me. [?]
Oh really?
It was me.
From now on, BABYMONSTER's algorithm
is in Spotify's hands.
[Let me hear you!]
Should we start dancing?
[I'm ready]
[Me too unni]
[Let's CHOOM]
[Ready to own it BABYMON?]
[Baby cheetah incoming]
Show us ASA!
[Watch me do it right]
[We love noona's fox energy]
[We gon get this party started!]
[RUKA time]
[World-devouring level of charisma]
[The host is obsessed]
The reaction is so good!
The time has finally come.
[Album name = Title track name] We are back with our 3rd Mini Album "CHOOM".
[MONSTER party begins now]
It's a powerful BABYMONSTER track
that shows our ambition
to showcase our dancing.
The album and title track have the same name,
it's a very straightforward title.
[CHOOM] it's a very straightforward title.
The production crew
heard our song
and started their own dance party. [?]
I feel like the camera crew
is internally dancing while filming us.
If you love 'CHOOM',
make some noise!
Thank you.
[Spotify S2 BABYMONSTER]
How did you feel
when you first heard the title track 'CHOOM'?
I liked the title right away.
'CHOOM'.
Having the single word
'CHOOM' as the title felt really cool.
When I heard the beat in the intro,
that's when I felt like this.
Wow...
[The beat already ate]
[We all felt it]
It sounded so cool,
and got me excited for the choreography.
When I heard the lyrics,
the whole theme was 'let's dance together',
so I thought it was the perfect title
to connect with fans and the public.
That made the lyrics leave a strong impression.
Speaking of the lyrics,
even just seeing them alongside the album cover,
you can instantly feel the energy.
What's the message behind it?
Mon Tue Wed Thu Fri Sat with BABYMONSTER.
Let's go all out and have fun.
What about Sunday?
What do we do on Sunday?
We have to sleep.
[Even BABYMONSTER takes Sundays off]
[Strict 6-day work week?]
We're not dancing then?
We danced all week long.
[Sleeping Beauty RUKA on Sundays] I have to rest.
After one day off, we're starting all over on Monday, right?
[Infinite 'CHOOM' routine]
Just like the lyrics,
which energizer member
is most likely to dance all week without getting tired?
I think it'd be
AHYEON?
[Unanimous vote from BABYMONSTER]
Our concerts last around two hours,
and even through the encore,
AHYEON keeps running around and pours energy into the performance.
[AHYEON with A+++ energy]
AHYEON said she wants to do endless encores at concerts.
You're making this public?
[Are you listening MONSTIEZ?]
Which song do you want to do the endless encore with?
To me, the best song
is whatever the fans love.
Fans always seem to enjoy this one.
[Totally]
We didn't get to perform 'DRIP'
for the encore at our fan concert.
We should do a remix,
or loop the song,
[Don't even think about leaving MONSTIEZ] so the fans never have to go home.
[I'm for real right now]
I can practically hear the fans cheering already.
You heard that, right?
What's your favorite line from the title track?
I kept thinking
this might be the song's killing part.
RUKA's
"I'll show you my every choom choom choom".
The lyrics are great on their own,
but aside from that,
RUKA put in a lot of thought into that part.
I could tell she was trying out lots of different things,
which got me even more excited for it.
Show us! Show us!
[Dance club sunbae coming through]
[Too much hot girl energy]
[Noona, you got me blushing]
[Destroyed]
[Respect]
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh!
[Did you see that, world?]
[Yes, and I'm loving you for life]
MONSTIEZ just screamed right now.
[MONSTIEZ status: vocal cords destroyed]
Other than this part,
was there any part during recording
that you paid extra attention to?
We spent a really long time recording 'CHOOM'.
We recorded it
over a long period of time.
Usually, recording takes
about an hour to an hour and a half for each member,
but this time it took us three hours.
[It's true]
The final part
was fun to do together.
[Group sing-along]
[Dance track made for automatic sing-alongs]
[Are you singing with us MONSTIEZ?]
[Choom choom choom choom]
[This is fun]
I'm so excited to see this at our concert.
CHIQUITA, was there a part you especially worked hard on
or focused on during the recording?
My part in the chorus goes,
[ASA does it too]
Let's choom...
But it kind of,
[Literally indescribable]
Let's choom.
They said this sounded too bright.
I was told to make it darker.
Let's choom.
I had to do this multiple times.
Was it difficult?
Yes.
Sometimes, it's harder to express something
with just one word than with a bunch of lyrics.
That vibe...
It was hard to catch that vibe.
You expressed that intense feeling very well.
Thank you.
[Thank you for killing the recording]
Since both the album and title track are called 'CHOOM',
this promises a powerful performance.
What would you say is the choreography's standout part?
The one during the chorus.
Twerking.
Could RUKA and CHIQUITA show us together?
MONSTIEZ around the globe are watching through Spotify.
[Eyes locked in, right?]
Hi. [?]
Show us!
[Eldest-youngest duo will CHOOM for real]
[Right now, it's the 'CHOOM' challenge BOOM]
[The dance all the cool dancers are doing these days]
[RORA came to CHOOM too]
[Twerking starts now]
[Squeal]
[Entire planet: jaw dropped]
The crowd is going crazy.
The performance is just as impressive as the lyrics.
Is there another member's killing part that you wanted for yourself?
It's not that I wanted the killing part,
but there's a funny story involving the same part.
Can I share it?
PHARITA and I do the same part.
[1st verse] [2nd verse]
About this part,
by the way, I love you chief producer.
Our chief producer always gives us feedback.
PHARITA has really long arms,
and there was a time
I didn't raise mine as much during this move.
CP: "AHYEON, your arms look a little short."
[LOL]
CP: "AHYEON, you know PHARITA has naturally long arms."
CP: "I think you need to extend your arms more."
After that, I only wore long sleeves
[Our girl's doing full-body stretching] and stretched my arms this high.
[Her cuteness stretched all the way up too]
[Upset] [Her cuteness stretched all the way up too]
[Babying the little sister] Your arms are definitely long enough.
[Why unni why] Why are your arms so long?
Why don't you meet in the middle?
PHARITA can make hers a little shorter,
and AHYEON can reach out longer.
[Mutual agreement has been made]
[PHARITA living up to the long-arm reputation]
[Hehe]
A mission just came in.
[Surprise Mission: 30-second b-side advertisement time]
[30-second mission?]
One member has to become a commercial model for 30 seconds,
and introduce three b-side tracks using three required keywords.
[Every word on the shuffle table must be used!]
[Starting with PHARITA]
Let's check out the ad right now.
[What keywords will she get?]
[Beautiful devils] [Umbrella] [Coffee]
Uh... stay by my side.
[With her emotional support RUKA]
First of all,
BABYMONSTER is
beautiful little devils to girls everywhere.
We sing 'MOON'.
It's a great song.
Please listen to it.
Listen to 'I LIKE IT' too.
Whether you're holding an umbrella, or holding coffee,
listen while sipping your coffee.
Please show lots of love.
I love you!
[That took 40 seconds]
She used all three words
and all three b-side tracks,
but failed because she exceeded the time limit.
This is hard.
I'm looking forward to the next member.
[Next up is AHYEON]
Hello,
I'm BABYMONSTER's AHYEON.
If you want to experience the beautiful devils,
listen to 'MOON'.
If you want a romantic vibe with an umbrella in hand,
then listen to 'I LIKE IT'.
What about pairing 'LOCKED IN' with a cup of coffee?
[Still not listening?]
[Puss-in-boots but make it AHYEON]
[Umbrella and coffee sales skyrocketing]
[So proud] [RORA is younger by the way]
Did I do it right?
[You're right, unni is always right]
Can you hear the Spotify streams going up?
[Spotify server exploded(?)] Can you hear the Spotify streams going up?
[Yay!]
[Stream 25 hours, 366 days a year]
[Certified devil of advertising]
Shall we check out
the next topic?
[What is RECORD MONSTER?]
Aren't you curious?
You're so curious, right?
[So I came prepared] We will find out through the 1st BABYMONSTER Spotify Streaming Exam.
[I'm gonna be the Streaming Exam winner!]
[Streaming Exam cruising along with the genius host]
[But] Are you ready?
[Anxious] Yes.
[Surprise present prepared by the host(?)]
What should I do?
[Life as BABYMON's youngest is tough]
[Demanding job: BABYMONSTER maknae]
[What trial awaits 18-year-old baby CHIQUITA?]
[Find out on K-Pop ON! Video Podcast]
[All the parts will be shuffled]
What happens if our parts get swapped?
It looks like we're singing each other's parts.
[BABYMONSTER's 1st attempt — let's get into Shuffle Live]
This is our first time switching parts.
We gotta have fun with it.
[Nervous] Let's do this.
[Full pack of anxious puppies]
[Who gets the first part?]
Come on out...
[Jumpscared RUKA]
[Awkward]
[RUKA scurrying]
[Oh! My turn]
[On thin ice]
[Shuffle Live stumbling its way forward(?)]
[Kinda timid...?]
[Even our energizer AHYEON...]
[Shuffle Live]
[Shuffle Live failed]
[Reason for failure: lack of confidence]
[What do we do if the K-Pop monsters lose confidence?] We weren't doing that bad.
[Unleash your inner MONSTER part 2]
Do you want another shot?
[We'll do better this time]
Give us one more chance...
Please.
[Begging for a retry]
[Fox noona's fatal stare]
[Spotify has been defeated]
[Earned another chance]
[Shuffle Live 2nd attempt]
[Now with extra confidence]
[Please let us succeed]
[Why are the live-performance queens this nervous]
Wait, wait.
It won't be me... right?
[RUKA, hurry!]
[RUKA scurrying again]
[Are we failing again?]
[Ayy]
[Unnis, baby's got this]
[Did you see that?]
[You get a million gold stars]
[Late from biting her finger]
[-1 point for being tardy]
[Mesmerizing points +10000000]
[Go get it panda!]
[AHYEON pulling up]
[That's our girl!]
[Fun!]
[Starting to loosen up a little]
[Members, you ready?]
[All set]
[Our host]
[Baby Jang Do-youn in her element]
[Dear world, you earned this song]
[Shake it]
[Mon Tue Wed Thu Fri Sat]
[Let's all get lost in]
[AHYEON]
[Watch out watch out]
[ASA go!]
[Vroom vroom]
[Poof!]
[CHIQUITA let her guard down!]
[Maknae? I'm big sis RUKA today!]
[RUKA status: proud fox]
[Risky] Gotta... keep it...
[Back on track]
[I'll show you]
[my every choom]
Do this! Do this!
[RUKA fox squad assemble]
[Just a cute little baby cheetah]
[That's our CHIQUITA]
[Part owner can't stop smiling]
[Billingitbillingit(?)]
[Show(?)]
[Unknown language detected]
[But their live vocals are always jaw-dropping]
[Around here, I'm a]
[Right here, right now with RORA]
[Hypnotized by RORA]
[I need BABYMON as my girlfriend now]
[This is grown woman aura]
[It's PHARI time!]
[Clap clap clap]
[Feeling lightheaded because ASA is the light]
[Swallow the whole world]
[RUKA scurrying forever]
[CHIQUITA caught off guard again]
[Haha]
[Unnis, you'll play with CHIQUITA, right?]
[Obvi]
[Not complete without scurrying RUKA]
[Why is our eldest going this hard lol]
[Princess RORA's side profile + voice attack]
[As the darkness falls deep]
[Okay bye]
[Now MONSTER party]
[At the MONSTER party, we have ASA noona]
[And baby CHIQUITA] [Cutie]
[Sending out the final boss]
[Her own part]
[Tear it up]
[Song's almost over — we can see the finish line!]
[Dance queen's favorite twerk move]
[Are we at BABYMONSTER's concert or what?]
[Just vibe]
[That's right]
[Shuffle Live by the boss girls who own the stage]
[Shuffle Live: huge success]
[We did it]
[Expected nothing less from them]
Thank you so much. [?]
For giving AHYEON her own high note part.
[Just the random shuffle at work] Thank you very much.
This is fun.
[What's the next shuffle?]
[See that? — Shuffle Live just set the K-Pop standard]
[Loved it]
How was that?
Shuffle Live was fun, right?
[No words needed]
[So fun]
This was one of the things we said
we wanted to try for an encore if we won first place.
[1st place pledge idea: part switch]
Let's count this as practice.
[Rehearsal for their music show win]
[Can't wait]
Along with 'CHOOM',
where can we listen to all the songs
from BABYMONSTER's 3rd Mini Album?
[Which record will the shuffle land on next?]
[Oh?]
The data from before
turned into emojis.
Where did these emojis come from?
Spotify?
[Where could it be?]
They're from the people who know BABYMONSTER
just as well as the Shuffle Table.
MONSTIEZ sent in the special data.
[That's so cool]
When did MONSTIEZ send this?
Seriously, when did you even send this!
[Very well played]
[Aegyo]
[RORA's aegyo...?]
[Hold up MONSTIEZ]
[Huh?]
Wait a second, I was supposed to be
the respected host today...
[lol]
You all have to
copy my aegyo exactly.
That won't be easy.
[What]
I'm going to show you a three-step aegyo for MONSTIEZ.
Don't leave anything out,
don't change anything,
and copy it exactly as it is.
[Most stressed person right now]
[Sigh...] [Most stressed person right now]
[Moment of crisis for the star host]
Here I go!
[Excited]
One, two, three.
[Pout]
[I can't watch...]
Second one!
[Cheek poke]
[I'm so proud of you]
[Ang]
[No caption]
Did you see that?
[???: How did the last one go again?]
[Messing with the host 1] How did the last one go again?
[Messing with the host 2] Show us one more time.
[These unnis...]
[1. Ooh]
[2. Ang]
[3. Cheeseburger]
[Pfft]
Oh! It was a cheeseburger?
It's a cheeseburger!
I thought it was a heart.
Cheeseburger.
[Nom!]
[Me too, nom]
Okay, shall we try it...?
[Time for everyone to follow the host's aegyo] I have high expectations.
[MONSTIEZ is watching]
[Spotify is testing me today]
[Let's go AEGYO MONSTER]
[Like an aegyo class teacher]
[Good job...]
Our members gave it their all today.
[100 out of 100 for effort]
Let's move on to the next message.
[Fashion?]
I'm a MONSTIEZ who signed up for a dance academy earlier this year.
I've never learned how to dance,
so I want to at least dress like I can,
but nothing I wear looks cool.
My aesthetic inspiration is ASA.
Please share some tips to recreate ASA's viral practice room look
which has become so iconic that people are saying,
"Only ASA can pull this off."
[A message for dance and fashion empress ASA]
[Oh my] [A message for dance and fashion empress ASA]
[Even more hyped]
[ASA's daily fashion = highly suggested] You're known for having next-level fashion sense.
[Any advice for the MONSTIEZ struggling with fashion?]
Since you said you're learning to dance,
you should try the look I wore in the short-form video.
Wear a hoodie with the hood pulled up, and a hat, and pull up one side
[Doing her unni's moves]
so one arm is exposed.
If you do that,
you'll give off major dance pro vibes!
[Yooo]
I'm curious.
ASA, what do you think of 'only ASA can pull this off'?
It's my first time hearing it.
Are you pleased with it?
Yes.
[Definitely happy about it] I feel great.
If you're a MONSTIEZ,
don't think 'only ASA can pull this off'.
Fashion is something we can share and try together.
If you wear the same outfits
or accessories we've worn before,
it might make us feel like we're connected.
Through fashion,
It'd be nice to interact and share that feeling.
Do you have any practice-room style aesthetics or tips?
When you dance,
wearing baggy clothes
makes your movements look bigger.
[Great tip]
I feel like wearing leggings
makes the vibe a little less hip...
But all of us wore leggings when we were trainees.
[RORA]
I used to wear leggings as a trainee.
Two layers at a time. [Lol]
[Self-callout] It was cold!
[Apparently it was cold lol]
[Witness 1] The socks! They were the highlight!
[Witness 2] Black T-shirt and leggings.
[Endless witness reports] With the white socks.
[RORA not found] Pulled up to here!
[AHYEON entered the chat] The leggings with stripes!
[Okay, and?]
I have a question.
How many leggings do you own?
[RORA leggings case file]
When I was a trainee,
I had tons.
[Baby Dain's leggings era] I used to love them.
But all of us wore them.
[BABYMONSTER comes clean]
I wasn't the only one dressing like that.
[YG trainee dress code(?)] It was a signature look.
It was tradition.
But trainees nowadays
dress really stylish.
[You were born in 2008] You're saying nowadays?
[08 baby already saying 'kids these days'?]
Then I guess you were
kind of old-fashioned back then.
[Excuse me]
Let's move on.
[Leggings phase Dain was so cute]
Hello, I'm a former study abroad student and current part-timer MONSTIEZ.
My dream is to become a world-class interpreter
and meet the BABYMONSTER members.
To make that dream come true,
I went abroad and studied really hard,
but I had to come back to Korea due to family circumstances.
I remember crying my eyes out on the flight back home.
These days, I'm working part-time at a cafe,
trying to stay strong while waiting
for the day I can finally achieve my dream,
but it hasn't been easy.
Could you comfort me with a song?
[A MONSTIEZ in need of comfort]
If you have a song you listen to
whenever you need comfort,
I think it'd be nice to sing it for MONSTIEZ.
I have one!
It's 'Niji' by Aqua Timez.
[I know it]
[It's okay, if we look up]
[It's alright, see, the seven-colored bridge]
[We can finally laugh together under the same sky]
[Ascended after hearing Angel RURU's voice] It's been so long since I heard your vocals.
[What message of comfort does the song carry?] Could you tell us about the lyrics?
The lyrics tell you,
it's okay.
Just like this...
Look at the sky.
There's a rainbow.
[Hearing the explanation made it even more comforting]
[Well-known song that gives hope and support to youth]
For me...
BLACKPINK's 'Love To Hate Me'
is a song I really like.
The lyrics of that song
are also about loving yourself a little more,
and taking time to reflect on yourself.
[A song AHYEON recommends and personally found comfort in]
[Love that]
[I'm cured thanks to the vocal genius]
[Final RECORD]
Shall we check it out right now?
How did you like the new records
BABYMONSTER created today?
[Our records today?]
There aren't many places for us
to fully express our own stories.
This was another chance
for our fans to get to know us better,
so I was really happy.
We also got to
talk a lot about "CHOOM",
which was great.
Plus, our host
did such an amazing job.
[Touched]
[Couldn't agree more] You're improving more and more.
Can we look forward to MC RORA in the future?
If you call me, I'm there.
[Baby Yoo Jae-suk, baby Jang Do-youn always on standby]
Please call her!
[Manifesting MC RORA!]
We are back with our new Mini Album.
It was really fun to play games on Spotify,
and introduce our album as well.
We also have concerts scheduled for June 26, 27, and 28.
[Please come see us]
Thank you so much Spotify for having us here.
I hope you guys enjoyed this.
And you can also listen to our new Mini Album "CHOOM"
on Spotify!
[Perfect ending]
This has been BABYMONSTER, ready to take over the world with 'CHOOM',
And our host.
[Born-to-be-MC RORA]
[A worldwide dance party with BABYMONSTER]
What was that?
You want to hear more stories from BABYMONSTER?
Then go to Spotify right now,
and look up K-Pop ON! Video Podcast!
[Bye]